We're giving up on the Ring of Wind?
要放棄風之戒?
While we dilly-dally here,
我們在這裡磨蹭的時候
the Abyss King's army is probably approaching.
深淵王的軍隊可能正在逼近
We can't stay here forever.
不能一直在這裡原地踏步
But...
可是…
We're not giving up on the ring but coming back for it later.
不是放棄 而是晚點再來
Our priority is collecting as many rings as possible.
現在必須盡早取得更多的戒指
With your current strength,
畢竟現在的你
you're no match for the Abyss King's knight.
連深淵王的騎士都打不過
You have a point.
話是這麼說沒錯…
Are you concerned about the princess?
你很在意那位公主嗎
Yeah.
是啊
I feel like I've disrupted her peaceful life.
總覺得是我擾亂了她的生活
They are finally leaving.
他們總算踏上旅程了啊
The story of the Ring King is a myth
戒王什麼的
that even the seemingly immortal elves can't tell if it was real.
是連長壽的精靈 都無法辨別真偽的老掉牙故事
Our duty is to protect the people
現在活在這裡的人
living in this city.
才是我們該保護的對象
Prince Jade!
傑德殿下
What is it?
什麼事
Bad news!
不好了
The Abyssal Creatures have breached the gust barrier!
有深淵的魔物闖進暴風屏障內
What?
什麼
A powerful monster
聽說有一個強大的魔物
tore a hole in the barrier.
在結界上開了一個洞
It's sending in the other monsters!
把手下的魔物一個一個送進來
The barrier has been breached!
結界破洞了
A mere monster actually broke through
父母建立的結界
my parents' barrier!?
竟然被區區的魔物…
There are more monsters
而且聽說結界外頭
waiting to attack outside the barrier!
還潛伏著更多的魔物
Those are
那是…
Abyssal Creatures!
深淵的魔物
How did they get in?
怎麼會
Is the barrier not working?
不是有暴風屏障擋著嗎
That direction...
那個方向是…
They are headed for the palace!
王宮
Let's turn back, Satou.
回去吧 佐藤
The ring must be protected.
必須保護戒指才行
Yes.
好
Well, Satou...
那麼 佐藤…
TALES OF WEDDING RINGS
《婚戒物語》
Release the arrows!
快射箭
The monster breached the barrier.
魔物已經穿過屏障了
Are you ever going to come out?
妳一直躲著真的好嗎
My brother will figure it out.
皇兄會想辦法的
There's nothing I can do.
我什麼也做不了
I promised my mother I'd stay here
乖乖地待在這裡
and keep my head down.
是我和母后的約定
If that's what you want,
如果妳這麼想
feel free to stay here and turn into a statue.
就在那裡待到變成石頭吧
An elf with a dead heart will never live.
死心的精靈是沒有活路的
As I anticipated, you're after the Ring of Wind.
妳的目標果然是風之戒啊
You're using this chaos to lower the barrier
是想趁亂完全消除屏障
so your army outside can break through.
再引入外頭的大軍嗎
Not on my watch!
想得美
Is this
這就是…
the Abyss King's knight that attacked Nokanatika?
襲擊諾卡那堤卡的深淵王騎士嗎
But I can't back down.
但我不能退讓
I must protect
我必須守護
my parents' legacy!
父母遺留下來的東西
We made it in time.
趕上了啊
Ring King!
戒王
What are you doing here?
你回來做什麼
Let me be clear.
事先聲明
I didn't come back to save your neck.
我並不是為了你才回來
This is her home.
這裡是她的歸宿吧
I couldn't defeat you last time.
雖然上次束手無策
But today, I will.
但這次我會讓妳好看
I have plenty of power to take you down.
因為我現在的力量很充沛
Keep your eyes to the front!
好好看前面 看前面
If you fall here,
要是你在這裡倒下
the world is doomed.
這個世界就沒有未來了
Do not push yourself too hard.
你千萬別逞強
Of course. All that matters is to reach her in time.
當然 只要能趕走她就足夠了
Fool...
太蠢了
The swords won't cut her.
劍碰不到她
All magic attacks are negated.
魔法也全部被抵銷了
You're fighting a foe you can never hope to defeat.
明明沒有勝算還去挑戰對方
Satou is well aware of that.
這些佐藤都心知肚明
But no matter how strong the enemy is,
但是 無論對手多強多可怕
Satou will keep us safe.
佐藤還是會保護我們
I can say the same.
這點我也一樣
From the day
從我發誓
I swore to protect my sister, this has been my only purpose in life.
要保護妹妹的那一天起 我就只為了這件事而活
I must protect Nephrites!
我必須保護涅芙麗緹絲
I'll free her from the ring's curse!
讓她擺脫戒指的宿命
I knew this would happen,
雖然早就料到會這樣
but things aren't looking good.
但還是很不妙啊
I thought I'd be stronger than this.
我還以為能發揮更強的力量
Hime?
小姬?
It's nothing.
沒事
Stay safe.
你小心一點
I can't do it alone.
光靠我是不行的
If it's just me...
光靠我…
Hime, stay away.
小姬 妳離遠一點
Nephrites.
涅芙麗緹絲
It's me, Krystal.
是我 克莉絲朵
Satou... We should retreat.
佐…佐藤 我們先撤退吧
No can do.
那怎麼行
That thing is after the Ring of Wind.
那傢伙的目標是風之戒
So I can't run away.
因此我不能離開這裡
Ring King!
戒王
The Ring Princess of Light went to get Nephrites.
光戒公主去叫涅芙麗緹絲了
Hime?
小姬?
Why would she do that?
她為什麼要這麼做
She is doing this for you.
全都是為了你著想吧
You have a great wife.
你有一位好妻子呢
Let's buy her some time!
再稍微撐一下
Please.
拜託妳
Please marry Satou.
和佐藤結婚吧
We've never had a proper introduction.
這是我們第一次好好交談吧
Is it all right to speak as your peer?
用平輩的語氣聊天 妳能接受嗎
You can tell me if you don't like it.
如果討厭就直說喔
My parents
我的父母
died protecting me and the ring.
也是為了保護我和戒指而喪命
I know your duty to safeguard
守護戒指和戒指的繼承人
and inherit the ring
這個使命有多沉重
is a heavy burden.
我也明白
I find myself useless because I couldn't do anything
我也覺得只能被保護
except be protected by others.
什麼都做不了的自己很沒用
My parents sacrificed their lives
我父母是自己犧牲性命
to create the gust barrier.
創造了風之結界
They did it so I wouldn't have to inherit the ring.
好讓我不用繼承戒指
I can't betray their sacrifice.
我必須守護這份心意
We are not the same.
我跟妳不一樣
You are correct about that.
妳的確和我不一樣
However,
但是…
it's the reason you can still save everyone.
正因為如此 妳才能保護大家
You're not as helpless as I was.
妳跟當時的我不一樣
Everyone is fighting.
大家都在戰鬥
Your brother and the elder are all fighting
妳哥哥 長老還有大家
the Abyss King's knight, no matter how powerful it is.
不顧深淵王的騎士有多強
That's because
那是因為…
it's the responsibility of the ring bearers.
這麼做就是戒指持有者的責任
No!
不是的
Satou is risking his life
佐藤之所以戰鬥
to defend your home!
是為了守護妳的歸宿
That's the reason he is fighting!
他是為此而戰
Lord Satou...
佐藤陛下他…
He may not look like it,
別看佐藤那樣
but he is thoughtful.
他其實很體貼
He won't give up until the very end.
一定會戰到最後一刻
There's a possibility he might get killed.
甚至有可能死掉
But even so...
可是…
There's nothing I can do for him!
我已經什麼都無法為他做
I hate it,
雖然很不甘心
but I can't do it by myself!
但光靠我是不行的
Please save Satou.
拜託妳 救救佐藤
Please marry Satou.
和佐藤結婚吧
Can I really help?
我真的能幫上忙嗎
Hime! Nephrites!
小姬 涅芙麗緹絲
Nephrites! What are you doing here?
涅芙麗緹絲 妳怎麼來了
Brother, you can give me an earful later.
皇兄 請你晚點再罵我吧
Are you sure about this?
真的可以嗎
Yes.
可以
What are you two doing?
妳們要做什麼
Father! Mother! I'm sorry!
父皇 母后 對不起
The barrier is disappearing.
風之結界漸漸消失了
What happened?
怎麼會這樣
Lord Satou!
佐藤陛下
This is bad.
情況不妙
Without the barrier,
要是沒有屏障
hordes of monsters will swarm in!
魔物大軍就會湧入
Don't worry.
沒事的
Lord Satou's Ring of Light
只要有佐藤陛下的光之戒
and Ring of Wind can take care of them.
和風之戒在就行了
Incredible.
好厲害
Satou, this is it!
佐藤 趁現在
Yeah!
好
I can command the wind!
我可以操控風
Hime... Nephrites...
小姬 涅芙麗緹絲
I...
我…
You're finally awake.
你醒啦
I expected nothing less from the man chosen by the Ring of Light.
不愧是被光之戒選中的人
That was quite a display of the rings' might.
你發揮了戒指的強大力量
Ring King.
戒王陛下
I must thank you
謝謝您拯救我國洛姆加
for saving the nation of Lomka from the Abyss King's army.
擺脫深淵王的威脅
I thank you
我代替洛姆加公主
on behalf of Princess Nephrites Lomka.
涅芙麗緹絲·洛姆加向您道謝
Who... Who is this?
您…您是哪位
The older sister of the late empress of Lomka,
這位就是前任洛姆加皇后的姊姊
Princess Sumaragdi.
絲瑪拉格蒂殿下
I thought she left the country
她…她不是在以前
after losing her lover
因為戒指失去愛人
to the ring.
離開這個國家了嗎
Why are you here?
為什麼會在這裡
Don't you remember
你不記得了嗎
the knight wearing a mask?
深淵王騎士面具下的那張臉
The Abyss King's knight
深淵王騎士的真面目
was actually the lost princess?
竟然是以前的戒指公主
See?
你看
A black Ring of Wind.
黑色的風之戒
That thing seemed to have controlled her mind.
她好像就是被這個操控了
But now, it's powerless.
不過它現在已經失去力量
I cursed my ill fate with the Ring of Wind
我當時詛咒必須繼承戒指的命運
and the world that forced me into accepting reality.
還有強迫我接受的世界
That dark thought
而這個醜陋的想法
gave him the opening.
被他趁機利用了
Pick up the ring.
拿起戒指
I'll free you from the suffering and pain.
我就拯救妳脫離苦海
The Abyss King would go as far as this?
深淵王那傢伙 竟然是這麼深不可測的人嗎
From what we know,
我們只知道
the Abyss King lost his physical form
他在與傳說中的戒王一戰後
after the great battle with the first Ring King.
就失去肉體
His soul was sealed far away in the north, at a place known as Varna.
靈魂被封印在遙遠的北地"梵納"
That's all we know.
僅此而已
But even without his form,
但是 就算看不見形體
the Abyss King's familiars never stopped attacking the humans.
深淵王的眷屬仍然不斷襲擊人們
And given his power to create black rings for his knights,
再加上能創造出 深淵王騎士的黑色戒指
the threat is more than apparent.
威脅很顯然存在
I see.
這樣啊
I need to collect all the rings as soon as possible and end this.
那我得快點收集到所有戒指 讓這件事早點結束
Satou!
佐藤
I'm feeling light-headed.
總覺得頭好暈
You used a massive amount of the rings' power.
你才剛用了戒指的龐大力量
It would've killed a normal king instantly.
換作是普通的王早就死了
You only feel exhausted
只有這點程度的疲勞
because your bond with the two princesses protected you.
是因為兩位公主的情誼守護了你
You should thank them.
要好好感謝她們
The two princesses...
兩位公主…
Yeah.
對喔
We married in the end.
我最後還是結婚了
I married another girl.
跟小姬以外的公主
But I...
但是我…
Nephrites...
涅芙麗緹絲
Lord Satou!
佐藤陛下
There is a healing spring in the palace.
王宮裡有一處泉水擁有治癒的力量
Let me take you there.
我帶你過去吧
You'll be good to go in no time.
一定很快就能好轉的
What is going on now?
這是什麼情況
Yes.
是…
I know how deep your love for each other goes.
我知道你們兩位深愛著彼此
I'd like to ask Princess Krystal for some guidance
我想請先成為妻子的克莉絲朵殿下
since she became your wife before I did.
教教我身為妻子該做些什麼
Wh...
什…
You're right.
也對
Satou and I really love each other a lot.
我和佐藤的確是很恩愛的關係
We've kissed so many times!
也接過很多次吻
Many times?
很多次
We do what couples do at night,
當然 晚上該做的事
and we do it every single night!
也是每晚做個不停
Huh!?
什麼
Every night...
每晚…
I see.
原來如此
Show me
那就讓我看看
how you cultivated this love of yours.
你們是怎麼培養愛情的
I had a lot of intimate experience with the human here,
雖然我和這個世界的人類 纏綿過很多次
but despite sharing the same looks,
但是異界的人類
the methods could be different from those from another world.
即使外表相同 做法可能也會有所不同
This is a perfect chance
這是難得的好機會
for me to observe the whole process.
就讓我在旁邊仔細觀摩吧
Come on.
快點…
Nephrites, watch and learn.
涅芙麗緹絲 妳看好了
Hime?
小姬
Hold on, Hime...
等等 小姬
This is the perfect chance, Satou.
佐藤 這是好機會
At least I won't falter at this moment.
現在的話 我就不能打退堂鼓
Hold on, Hime!
等一下 小姬
I'm not going to let the mood of this place
我才不會被這種氣氛
control my mind!
牽著鼻子走
You are the Great Sage.
既然你是人稱的賢者
Do you know anything
不知道你知不知道
about the young traveller
50年前
who came here 50 years ago?
來過這裡的年輕旅行者
He was my love.
我所愛的那個人
Was he killed?
究竟是被殺掉了
Or did he escape alive?
還是順利逃過一劫
That was my gift to him!
那是我送給他的東西
Where did you get it?
怎麼會在你手上
The two of us have known each other for ages.
我從以前就跟他很熟
Is he still alive?
他還活著嗎
He once said,
他曾經說過
"I can't allow the woman I love to become estranged with her people
無法忍受自己深愛的女性
because of me."
因為自己的關係被大家疏遠
He now lives a peaceful life in a land far away.
他現在正在遙遠的土地 過著平靜的生活
I see.
這樣…啊
He's always wanted you to be happy.
他一直希望妳能過得幸福
I'm glad to have the chance to relay his thoughts.
能像這樣轉告妳真是太好了
Father. Mother.
父皇 母后
Until you become stronger,
直到妳變堅強之前
we will never stop protecting you.
我們都會守護妳的
I'm all right now.
我已經沒事了
Also, I've found a purpose.
而且我也找到想做的事了
Are you leaving?
妳要走了嗎
Brother.
皇兄
Yes. I am leaving.
對 我要走了
You've become so strong,
妳變堅強了呢
Neph.
涅芙
Lord Satou!
佐藤陛下
Nephrites.
涅芙麗緹絲
Are you sure about this?
這樣好嗎
Yes.
是的
Being with the Ring King and assisting him in his cause
待在戒王身邊 成為他的助力
is a Ring Princess' duty.
是戒指公主的職責
Besides,
而且
I want to see the outside world.
我也想多看看外面的世界
I want to visit
然後總有一天
Lord Satou's world someday.
我要去佐藤陛下生活的世界
That's a promise!
我們約好了吧
Satou, when did you say that?
佐藤 你說了這種話嗎
Oh...
嗯
Hey!
有沒有搞錯
You are unbelievable.
討厭 真受不了你
Will the Ring Princess find happiness,
這次的戒指公主能得到幸福嗎
Elder?
長老
No.
不對
You're one of the earliest Ring Princesses,
最早的其中一名戒指公主
Princess Peridot.
佩莉多特殿下
All the Ring Princesses I've met so far
我到目前為止見過的戒指公主
have never had happy endings.
都沒有什麼好下場
It was the same for the first Ring Princess.
第一代也是這樣
The new Ring King
新任戒王
is a bit too bashful for a king,
作為王雖然有點太含蓄了
but this quality of his might shift things in a better direction.
但說不定反而能讓事情 往好的方向發展
Has the Ring King left?
戒王陛下已經出發了嗎
Yes.
嗯
They should be out of Lomka's border by now.
應該已經離開洛姆加領地了
I see.
這樣啊
I'd like to see Great Sage Alabaster.
我真想見見大賢者阿拉巴斯塔一面
Alabaster?
阿拉巴斯塔?
That's him...
那個人就是…
What's the matter, Gramps?
怎麼了 爺爺
No, it's nothing.
不 沒什麼
Let's press on.
快走吧
I don't want to spend the night in the wild.
不快點就要露宿野外囉
Fine.
好好